Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO LIVING CREATURE WAS HARMED
DURING THE FILMING OF THIS SHOW.
Those tyrants are using our warriors
against us.
Come back to your true self, Göktuğ.
Don't forget, everything turns to it's
essence.
A dog is a dog, a wolf is a wolf!
Look, I have the same thing on me.
Of course, you have, son. All of our
warriors have that.
Balgay... You will pay for it, Balgay.
Your tears can't put out the fire
of your heart, brother.
I remember everything, one by one.
Our father...
Our mother...
What Mongols had done...
As long as this craven Balgay
lives, every breath is a sin for me.
What are you doing, Göktuğ?
Wait, brother.
I'll go there. I'll skin him alive.
I'll watch him bleed out until the last
drop of his blood, brother.
It's not the time to kill Balgay,
brother.
What are you saying, brother?
What are you saying after all he
has done?
Brother...
Sometimes, having your enemy alive is
better than being dead.
We need him alive for now.
You know, we made an alliance with him.
You will act as nothing happened.
You will, so that...
...we will strike him at a
good moment.
All those years that went to waste,
that you spent far from your essence...
...can only be recovered by the goodness
of penitence.
Now, repeat after me...
Eşhedü en la ilahe illallah...
...ve eşhedü enla Muhammeden
abdühü ve rasulü.
You should've seen Osman's face
when he found out that Zorba is dead.
His anger grew. It was like
he couldn't control it.
Osman's heart is great.
He is inclusive.
But so is his wrath.
He won't give up on this before
confronting Dündar.
End of this confrontation is clear,
Selcan Hatun. It won't be silent.
Wow... Selcan Hatun.
Yes, Burçin.
The fur flew.
Osman Bey screamed the place down.
You are sitting here.
We don't compete to learn and
involve in everything.
So, we learn what we need
when the time comes.
If so, you shouldn't hear
it from me.
Burçin... Say what you want
to say.
I said you shouldn't hear it from me.
Burçin... I owe so much to your deceased
mother. That's why I bear you.
But don't try your luck. Say what you
will.
Well, since you want it so much...
I should say it.
It wasn't good to see Osman saying that
on the day Aygül was about to marry.
What...did Osman do?
What do you think? Osman Bey came to
the tents with great rage.
He turned the place upside down by saying
''I won't let you marry Aygül to Alişar''
Burçin, what are you speaking,
my daughter?
What business would Osman has with
Aygül's marriage?
I don't know about that. Bamsı Bey and
Gündüz Bey barely managed to stop him.
They told him that he went beyond limit...
They didn't say enough but anyways.
What did Osman tell to Dündar that
made him went beyond the limit?
''I won't let Aygül marry to Alişar''
he said.
-What else did he say?
-What else should he say?
That was all his problem, after all.
What problem did Osman Bey
has with Aygül?
Eh... After all the hurly-burly...
...Dündar Bey spoke at last.
He revealed an old secret.
It seems that back in time he gave Aygül
to Osman.
It's obvious that Osman regretted it so
that he had done all these.
You hit my nerve, Selcan Hatun.
I said I shouldn't speak. You wanted it.
Look after Osman, my nephew.
He threatens us openly.
His anger controls him, uncle.
What's wrong, son?
What's on your mind?
Our anger is so strong, Bamsı Bey.
But if we lose our control to anger...
...it will harm us.
What will we do, brother?
What do you mean?
If we take my uncle in front
of the Tent, blood will be spillt.
We'll carry the banner of mercy like
we carry the banner of courage.
My uncle can't see further from the smoke
in front of him. Let him go to the wedding.
Alright, brother. But, what if we
help Alişar by doing that?
Alişar can think that he has everyone
in his hands...
And we won't be seen together...
...so, my uncle can get closer to you.
And then? Then what, son?
What's on your mind?
I'll confront my uncle with Alişar
to show that I didn't kill Batur.
So we will get rid of this boil
for good.
-How will this happen, brother?
-Thanks to Aygül, brother.
If everything comes to Aygül...
If Alişar plays all his games on Aygül...
So, we'll break all his games by Aygül.
Osman doesn't know what he speaks.
He does, nephew.
He does.
Look, I'm telling you.
If he tries to stop the feast...
...you should know that we won't
have any more words to speak.
When the dust rises up...
...eyes can't see clearly, Dündar Bey.
What more should I do, Bamsı Bey?
I tried to be his uncle...
...I tried to be his father...
...now he faces me and tells me that
I can't give Aygül to Alişar.
He went completely crazy.
If something happens to us,
it's on him.
Now, you steel yourself, Dündar Bey.
-I will try talking to him.
-That would be good.
He listens to your words, Bamsı Bey.
I couldn't find time in the rush.
One of you is the Bey of my tents,
and the other is...
...the elder of my tents.
I hope you won't leave me alone
in the feast.
Don't worry, uncle.
I won't leave you and Aygül alone.
-We'll be there at the wedding feast.
-Thank you, thank you.
Father, let me come with you.
The road isn't safe.
Do you still say ''father''
without any shame?
Are there any other danger than
your existence?
No need.
Keep your shadow away,
I want nothing more.
He doesn't want me, Gündüz Bey.
Let the wedding feast begin...
...maybe his heart can soften up.
Osman...
Maşallah.
I see you alive like this...
...I'm very happy, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Thank you, Osman.
Mashallah.
Ghazi's white beard swing like
battle banners, my bey.
He is powerful than any other soldiers.
There still are many weapons to swing
and many tyrants to beat, Osman.
One who follows the true path
always finds companions.
So, Abdurrahman Ghazi, tell me
about this thing.
Who is behind this cowardice?
Allah knows... I thought of Balgay
when we were ambushed.
But it was Alişar.
Alişar...
Don't kill Abdurrahman Ghazi.
And his right-hand man is on it.
Dündar didn't want us to be killed.
But Alişar took him away.
Alişar...
So, Alişar wants to oppress my uncle.
-It's true, Osman
-Things became complicated.
Nothing is complicated, Boran.
Alişar is behind every evil.
Allah knows that he is responsible for
Batur's death, as well.
Not only Batur's death but also
abduction of Princess Adelfa...
...and that Zorba incident.
Zorba was his closest man.
He must have known something
that Alişar didn't want us to learn.
And seen things that Alişar
didn't want us to see.
So, he sacrificed him.
So, Osman, what is the
role of Dündar?
He'll say that.
But all the mysteries come together
on the name of Alişar.
What will we do, my Bey?
What's on your mind?
We'll teach Alişar not to play with us.
-Abdurrahman Ghazi.
-Yes, Osman.
You go to the mansion with
Kılıç Alp.
Follow him until he falls
to my trap.
Alright, Osman.
Kılıç.
I had the best room prepared for you,
Commander Böke.
Have a rest. Then we'll talk about
what happened.
You have your grave prepared.
When Geyhatu learns what happened,
he will have you buried alive in there.
Will I answer for your clumsiness,
Commander Böke?
You are at least as much as responsible
of this as I am.
Our secret associate with Sofia is no
longer a secret.
Geyhatu will ask for this from
both of us.
We'll clean this mess together.
How?
We'll find Osman and kill him.
We will do it together.
Do you think that Osman's corpse can
revive ours?
I haven't played my last move yet.
I'll make contact with Sofia and do what
needs to be done.
Osman will die. He must.
Osman is more dangerous than we think.
Osman captured Genghis Khan's Law.
He stopped Geyhatu and Princess Adelfa's
marriage.
He found the tracks of Margareth Monks.
He can't do it all alone.
He wasn't alone. He had someone with him.
-Who was it?
-His uncle. Sungur Tekin
All troubles are after me.
-What is the situation?
-It will be done in a minute, my Bey.
C'mon, hurry. Alişar Bey is waiting
for us.
I told you that Alişar is not a friend!
But what have you done?
You took shelter under him. But it
wasn't enough, you also gave him Aygül.
If you cared so much of Aygül...
...then, when I told you to take her
as your wife...
...why did you refuse?
-I have spoken.
You should know that I won't let
Aygül marry Alişar.
Daughter...
Don't be sad.
It's a good thing. Horses can rest a bit.
The vision of my brother Batur doesn't
go away, father.
He isn't with me in this happiest
day of mine.
If he was here...
...would we be destitute like this?
He would be on your side.
He wouldn't let his sister be in that
state.
I put my valiant son to the grave,
all alone.
I'm taking my precious daughter
groom's house, all alone.
I'm like a parasite... In my own home.
For sure, this darkness won't last
forever.
Also, we've seen our real friends
and real enemies.
-We did.
We did, thanks to Allah.
We did.
Those who stood with me on my
bad times...
...those who didn't stand with me
on my light times...
They are all written down.
Not only Osman...
...whoever stands with him...
...I will confront everyone who
put us into this situation.
I will...
But...
...you shouldn't be sad today,
my pretty daughter.
You should smile.
Smile... Smile, so your father can
always remember you like that.
Smile... So, this helpless Dündar who has
you married...
...can heal his heart a little bit.
Come on.
My brother once said that
Osman Bey's compassion...
... is as strong as his sword.
Forgive me for my inhumaneness, Osman Bey.
Give your blessings.
From now on, in my eyes...
...you're the same with Konur.
Welcome to your roots, Göktuğ.
I have other news, my Bey.
My brother not only returned
to his roots...
... he also chose the true
religion of Islam and became a Muslim.
Praise be!
May Allah keep you in
the right path, brother.
Being your Alp, being enlightened with
the light of Islam...
... is my greatest honour.
May Allah always keep you with us.
May the rest of my life be
ruined on your path, Osman Bey.
Thank you, Göktuğ brother.
Thank you.
Now, brothers...
Listen to me carefully. Dündar Bey is
going to the mansion with the dowry car.
The Alps have loosened the car's wheel.
They will need to stop.
And then we will ambush
my uncle and his family.
My Bey, Dündar Bey will resist.
What will we do?
I want him alive.
I need him alive.
But Alişar will get the news fast.
Abdurrahman Gazi is after that dog.
Konur. Once Alişar leaves the mansion,
you will get Princess Adelfa from there.
But take the Princess somewhere safe.
As you order, my Bey.
After we attack Alişar's mansion,
not only with him, but we will also...
... become enemies
with Geyhatu, my Bey.
As you know, Böke is with him.
Its too late, Boran.
Now I'll be enemies with
the entire world if necessary.
Its time to be brave, brothers!
Remember, I don't want any mistakes!
Let's go!
- Allahu Akbar!
- Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest!)
Let's go!
Marinate these with honey.
There will be a wedding and
a feast after iftar.
What do you want from me?
- Osman.
- I don't know where Osman is.
Only thing I know is that he won't stop
before crushing the heads of...
...a rat like you and
a snake like Sofia.
You will pay for this, Alişar Bey.
You will dream of those when you're
rotting in Geyhatu's hareem.
I'd rather die than marry
that barbarian names Geyhatu.
Neither he nor I care whether if
you're Geyhatu's woman or not.
- Where is Osman?
- I wouldn't tell you even if I knew.
I give you a single chance to be free.
How does Osman know you?
Who from Byzantine is he working with?
Tell me everything you know!
Let's see if you can be
this brave once he is here, Alişar Bey!
Hang her to the ceiling from her arms.
Don't give her anything until she talks.
Let's see how long she'll last.
- It's more sturdy now, my Bey.
- Thank you.
If you allow, we're ready to get going.
We lost a lot of time.
Let's get going as soon as possible.
Hatuns! Let's go!
Let's go.
Ambush!
Osman!
What do you think you're doing?
Huh? What do you think you're doing?
We know what we're doing, uncle.
- Drop your weapon.
- What if I don't?
What if I don't? Will you kill me?
Not even the bandits ambush
a caravan going to a wedding.
Aren't you ashamed of what you're doing?
Is this how brave you are?
Be ashamed.
Alps! Drop your weapons!
Don't make us spill a brother's blood.
Do it.
Take my life.
Take my life!
Kill me! If you don't kill me,
I swear I'll kill you all one by one!
Take my life!
Take it!
Take my life.
Osman is going to ambush
my uncle Dündar...
... while he's going
to Alişar's mansion, aunt.
Osman wants to solve this
without spilling any blood.
He wants to hinder Alişar's game
by showing Aygül the truth.
Things will get out of control if any
blood is spilt, Allah forbid.
The Tent will light up from
the inside and...
... no one will be able
the put that fire out. You know that.
There is no other way, aunt.
Osman will use Dündar and Aygül
to lure Alişar into his trap.
There is no other way.
Dündar's Alps and Beys won't
be getting what they want.
My Osman will both make his uncle open
his eyes and expel this trouble of ours.
Now, we need to hold tight.
What about, Bahadır? Him appearing so
suddenly seems suspicious to me.
Bahadır is an orphan, aunt.
My uncle ignores him
so he's finding a place to stay in.
- No need to be suspicious.
- Son...
You don't travel harsh roads
with a soft heart.
Too much mercy will bring sickness.
I know, I understand that you're related.
But...
Don't be your feelings'
prisoner, my Gündüz.
Bamsı Bey is right, my Gündüz.
Dündar left the Tent.
But if you ask me...
His ears are still here.
What I mean is we need to be careful
about what we talk about next to Bahadır.
Maybe you're right, Bamsı Bey.
I will be alert without
breaking Bahadır's heart.
Don't you worry.
May Allah protect us.
- Amen.
- Amen, Selcan Hatun.
- I will go alongside Bala Hatun.
- Okay.
Thank you, Selcan Hatun. Thank you.
It seems that they gave Aygül to Osman.
It's obvious that Osman Bey regretted it
so he raised hell.
Osman! Oh Osman!
I won't let Alişar marry Aygül, he said.
Bala Hatun! Easy there.
Your speed is racing with
your shamelessness.
We kick you out of the door and
you get in through the chimney.
Aren't you ashamed?
You brought us bad luck.
How much blood
do you want to be spilt?
- Isn't it enough?
- Aygül sister...
If you have big dreams,
keep your heart strong.
It shouldn't fall in every struggle.
If you raise that hand to me again,
I'll pull your eyes out.
Bala Hatun!
Gündüz Bey said that
everyone must stay in the Tent.
- Giddy up!
- Bala Hatun! Where are you going?
What do you think you're doing?
Fear Allah!
Let me go!
You ambush your uncle with
Balgay's dog, huh?
Take our lives so we're
free from your malice, Osman.
You hurt a lot of people, uncle.
You won't be dying that easily.
You will pay for them first.
Come on. Get on the car.
We'll have a long talk with you.
Alişar is almost here.
What will you do to me if I resist?
- What will you do?
- I won't even touch you.
But Zöhre Hatun collaborated
with the enemy.
And my brother deemed her worthy of exile.
And I...
... will take her life right
in front of your eyes!
I'm afraid...
... you'll actually do that
to your uncle, Osman.
You'll do that too.
Konur. Take them to
the secret beech with Göktuğ.
Go to the mansion from there.
Dumrul and Ayaz stay alert.
Bala!
Bala, my girl!
Bala... My dark-eyed girl,
what did you do?
- Selcan Hatun!
- What?
Bala Hatun left the Tent on a horse!
Gündüz Bey's orders, no one
leaves, I said. She didn't listen.
She left in such a way that it looked
like her horse would burst!
What are you saying? Go after her!
Find Bala, come on!
My girl... What will I say to Osman
if we can't find Bala?
Only you'll understand
how I feel, my Alaca.
We thought we wore love as
wings on our backs...
But it was a rope on our necks instead.
See?
It left us short of breath.
Osman ripped our hearts out.
How can I live without
looking at these eyes?
I trusted you with my heart and my future.
I'm here if you protect them.
If you give up, I won't be mad.
Remember that.
Then...
...this is the promise of Osman the Black.
Remember well.
Wherever you go, I'm right behind you.
I swear!
We went through such incidents.
Such much has happened.
Osman put everything to
the side and said...
..."I won't let Alişar
marry Aygül", Alaca!
How can my heart not burn?
If he doesn't tolerate Aygül's marriage
that much...
...what can we say?
May Allah unite her with Osman bey.
My reliever is my father.
He will calm us down.
He'll give peace to our souls certainly.
Am I right?
Come on, my girl.
Come on!
You will regret.
But It will be too late.
Dündar Bey rules thinking about everyone.
Gündüz Bey rules at his will.
When everyone hears about this,
then I'll see what you do.
I don't know, Zöhre Hatun.
I do what Osman bey orders.
Where is my father?
Where did you take him to?
Are you afraid of two women whose
hands are tied?
You don't have the right to know that.
I am not allowed to say that as well.
Now, be silent.
I'll do my job.
Come on.
Do you take pleasure doing
this to your uncle, Osman?
You did it, uncle.
A lot of soldiers of us died just
because of you.
Also, you killed my son.
Moreover, you tried to kill me.
If you feel comfortable about this,
kill me here.
You're carrying my ancestor blood.
I can't take responsibility by
killing you.
I curse the day you were born!
You're testing my patience.
Do you think I don't know that
you are doing some dirty things?
From where did you find the laws of
Cengizhan, Osman?
That princess you brought to Tent...
Who says something to you?
Who is chasing you down an alley?
Who is behind you, Osman?
Whose pawn have you become that you
help them?
Answer.
I have my limits and you exceeded it.
Now, answer me like a man.
Don't ever tell a lie.
I know everything.
Everything!
Do you know why I'm not killing you,
uncle?
Because you are putty in the hands
of Alisar.
I don't kill you because I feel
sorry for you.
I know that you prevent Alisar so that
he couldn't kill Abdurrahman Gazi.
I know that his dog, Melik, is trying
to kill Abdurrahman Gazi without mercy.
How do you know these, Osman?
Abdurrahman Gazi and Kılıç Alp are alive.
I learned everything from them.
Dündar Bey should have come till now.
He is about to arrive.
He'll come now, my bey.
Adorn everywhere with spring flowers.
I want to welcome Aygül Hatun with
pretty scents.
Why are you behaving like that when we
have that much of trouble, Alişar Bey?
Is it because you're going to marry?
Our job is hard when there is huge Kayı
Tent behind Osman.
Didn't you understand it still, commander
Böke?
The ring I'll wear on Aygül's finger
will be a collar for her father.
If you take Kayı Tent against you
in these lands...
...you'll be surprised like Balgay
sooner or later.
We'll see.
From now on, the lady of my mansion is
Aygül Hatun.
Tell the workers that they should do
whatever she wants.
Order is order, my bey.
What do you want?
There has been a raid in Karaca, my bey.
Bandits have taken a vehicle.
There are blood trails.
They're new.
Vehicle?
What's happening, Alişar Bey?
Get the soldiers ready right now,
Melik.
And my horse.
Hurry!
Where are you going, Alişar Bey?
Dündar Bey should have come till now.
There is something we don't know,
commander Böke.
Do you think it is Osman?
Osman is the cause of every disaster.
Now, we'll understand.
Let's go.
Bring it quickly!
The jackal got out of his mansion.
Abdurrahman Gazi is alive, huh?
Your every word is a lie.
My word is right as much as
I didn't kill your son Baturay.
Alişar kidnapped you from
Abdurrahman Gazi, not Balgay.
In order to use you by hiding your faults
and provoking you, uncle.
Open your eyes!
Don't you see, uncle?
There is lie and hypocrisy
in every word of you, Osman.
The dog of Balgay, Kongar.
He was even with you.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Will you deny that as well?
Don't you realize that I know you made alliance
with Balgay to ascend the throne of Kayı?
If I wanted to do so, I would have killed
you already, uncle.
Osman...
Who knows what're you trying to do?
Who knows what're you waiting for?
Aren't you the one that sacrifice
his own daughter for greed?
Your son, Batur, died because of your
greed.
You don't even see that Alişar
who you'd trusted so much killed your son.
That's enough.
That's enough, Osman.
I don't believe any word of you.
In order to comfort yourself,
you ignore even the truth.
You've always wanted my father throne.
With his absence, you couldn't stop
being greedy.
You're doing business with Alişar who
you're suspicious for killing your son.
That's enough, Osman.
That's enough!
That's enough.
I promise...
I'll kill you with my own hands one day.
Either kill me here today or
wait the day you will die.
I'll confront you with Alişar, uncle.
When you hear the truth from him...
...your death will be because of your
grief, not because of me.
Boran.
Yes, my bey.
Take my uncle from here.
I don't want to see him.
Osman.
One day, there will be doomsday.
Aunt?
What happened, Selcan Hatun?
Why're you worrying?
Bala Hatun has gone.
Where, aunt?
He heard the words of Osman saying
that he won't allow Aygül to marry Alişar.
She was confused.
I couldn't think of it.
Everybody knows the love of Osman.
Why did she behave like this?
Because of her love, Bamsi Bey.
When she heard the words of
Osman saying he won't allow her...
...she couldn't stay there anymore.
I get her followed.
But I don't think she will be found.
What are we gonna do?
Wait, wait, aunt.
We'll find a solution surely.
We should find, or else I have
nothing to say Osman, son.
This is the mark of Kayı.
The fight has occurred in here.
There is blood trail on the floor.
Janissary headgear of Dündar Bey.
His headgear is here, but
he's not here.
The clash has occurred in here but there
isn't any corpse.
It's apparent that he wants you
to come somewhere.
Let's follow the traces.
Didn't you understand till now that
how wise guy Osman is, Melik?
Do you think a troublesome guy like
Osman will leave evidence behind him?
If you follow the traces, the only
thing you'll find is your grave.
What're we going to do, my bey?
There is only one thing to be done.
I'll go to Kayı Tent and call
them to account.
Then, let us come with you, my bey.
You stay with Böke.
Right. You know here well. There
is a lot of ways to pursue them.
Soldiers.
Gather whoever you find. You will
enter into commander Böke's service.
Alişar Bey.
I need Osman alive.
Don't forget that.
If we don't learn who is behind him,
after that we will be dead.
Now you take the bait,
Alişar.
Come on then!
You fall into the trap of Osman.
Come, Alişar.
Come.
Anyone didn't see you or hear you,
right?
You invited us, we came here as if
we were walking in water, Bahadır Bey.
No one saw and heard anything.
When Osman killed your brother Baturay,
your father stumbled a lot, Bahadır Bey.
Fortunately, you came back and
he reached the strength to endure.
Your coming back made him alive again.
But no one will know it.
Osman and his friends should think
I am in bad with my father...
...so that he has a deficit.
We feel the fire of revenge
in your heart.
We're proud of you, my bey.
Order and then we take our revenge.
Finally, that blessed time has come.
In the night of the wedding, We will spill
out hatred against them...
...and choke our enemies.
Why are we waiting for the wedding,
my bey?
The wedding will be in the mansion.
The people of Kayı and Bey's of Tent, they
will go to Eskihisar as a guest of Alişar Bey.
When they come back to the Tent,
their new Bey will greet them.
Where is my father, mother?
They didn't kill him, did they?
They didn't, my daughter.
Fortunately, my father.
Fortunately.
Fortunately, you're good, my bey.
Do you really call this situation good,
my wife?
May Allah help us.
Amen.
What're you doing, huh?
Where are you taking my daughter to?
Set free my daughter.
Dündar Bey!
What're you doing?
Boran.
Set free my daughter.
Set free!
Where are you taking my Aygül to?
Didn't we sort it out?
Osman Bey ordered so.
Boran!
Where are you taking my daughter to?
If something happens to my Aygül,
I swear I'll kill all of you...
...and establish Kayı Tent again
on your graves, Boran.
Boran!
Osman!
What's your problem with Aygül?
What are you planning?
What's your problem, Osman.
Osman!
Did you start to be bandit by putting
away the soldiery and morals, Osman Bey?
The bandit is walking around you, Aygül.
But you don't want to see.
I saw what I should see, Osman Bey.
You've killed my brother.
Now, you're being unfair to my family.
If I had wanted to kill him, I would have
killed Batur in front of the Tent.
But I didn't.
As for your family, Alişar
cheats them.
Alişar, huh?
Do you know who embraced us when we're
expelled from the Tent, Osman Bey?
Who saved my father and had him treated?
Who saved us from your cruelty?
Now you're talking about
the plans of Alişar.
Why did he do these things?
Is it just because he loves you so much?
I don't know how much he loved me or us.
But it's apparent that he loves us
more than you do.
Now that you were so fond of us, then...
...why didn't you marry me?
Aygül...
I loved you in a different way.
I saw you as my sister.
I wanted to protect you.
But...
you thought the other way.
You didn't see me as I see you.
What's my fault?
Am I supposed to marry you to protect you
and think about your own good?
Aygül...
Don't see me as a stranger just for
that I didn't see you as another way.
Don't hate me for not loving you back.
Your hate will burn your future now.
Alişar isn't a brave man as you think.
He wants to exploit you.
And I want to prevent it.
I...
...couldn't think about these, Osman Bey.
I wish you're happy with Bala Hatun.
Aygül, I love Bala Hatun.
But I said that I won't let Aygül
be with Alişar.
How can I help you more?
I need your help to show
the truth to everyone.
Help me like...
I help you.
What do you want from me, Osman Bey?
My uncle is still my uncle, although
he's done so many bad things.
I have to help him.
I will make him confront with Alişar.
I can't do it without your help.
Are you brave enough to see the truth?
I am.
Then listen to me.
Tell me, Gündüz.
Where is Dündar Bey?
He must have come to you.
You tell me where my uncle is.
I found Dündar Bey's cap in the woods.
There were traces around it.
What are you talking about, Alişar Bey?
As you see, Alişar Bey.
We don't know anything.
If you don't know, then
why don't you look for him?
I said I found his cap! Why
are you waiting!
I'll tell the Alps.
They will look for my uncle everywhere.
Alişar, you should know that...
if you have a finger in this situation
too...
you won't have a head...
...to wear a cap.
You should know that, Gündüz...
if your brother Osman has
a finger in it...
...you won't have a tent to be a Bey for.
Brother..
...let me go with him.
I'll let you know.
Look at us, Dündar Bey.
We're a mess.
His intention is clear, Hatun.
He'll get rid of us first.
We can't run away.
Osman bides his time.
It's us, then Gündüz and then...
...whoever he sees.
Osman will get rid of everyone
and rule the tent.
I hope he drowns in his greed.
I'm not afraid.
You're still Dündar Bey.
You have Alps and Beys.
It's not that easy.
You'll thank me because you're by my
side against ignoble Alişar.
But I'm so grateful for him, even
if you call him ignoble.
He protected me in such hard times.
My good-hearted sister.
You'll see who is Batur's killer and how
dangerous Alişar is for us...
...when you do whatever I say.
This marriage will be your mistake.
Your biggest regret.
Okay. What do you want?
I'll do whatever you want.
I hope we make it up as you said.
Now...
...you'll go to the palace and tell
him that...
" My father hides in the woods."
"He said we were abducted by Osman but
he learnt something big about Osman."
"He wants to talk to you alone."
"He said that you come alone."
"He said that you two finish him finally."
Bring Alişar to where I say and
I'll deal with the rest.
Do it and let's finish this fight.
- Salamun Alaikum, Osman.
- Alaikum Salam.
You wear armour before your wound heals.
You're in my war, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Give me your blessings.
I fought with your grandfather Süleyman
Shah, your father Ertuğrul Ghazi.
Thanks to my Allah...
I fight with you too.
- You give me your blessings.
- Thank you, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Thank you.
Did we trap Alişar?
As you said.
When Dündar is late, Alişar and Böke
went out of the palace.
They found Dündar's cap.
- He must have gone crazy.
- Yes, my Bey.
He went to the tent.
He'll fall into our trap when
my brother says nothing.
You should rest, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Kılıç Alp stays with me.
I'll let you know if anything happens.
Thank you, Osman.
My Sheikh, we've been wandering in
this wood for days.
Forgive me but...
...what are we looking for?
Our griefs, Zülfikar.
Our griefs.
The beginning of everything
starts with getting worried.
When the Quran honours the earth...
...those who believe just began
to understand oracles.
But there was someone who was
uncomfortable with his life.
He was worried about mankind and...
...he felt that in his heart.
That's why he settled in Mount Hira.
He was our Prophet.
He kept asking himself that...
"What should I do? What should I do?"
The first verses were about this grief.
These were the remedies of that grief.
Beard is a tradition
(in Islam), right Akça?
Yes, my Sheikh.
To greet is a tradition, right Zülfikar?
Eating with the right hand
is a tradition, right?
Yes, my Sheikh.
The most powerful tradition is...
...to let people have the oracles.
To grief with this.
Our Allah gives our Prophet's duty...
with the grief he has...
...like this in Al-Muddaththir surah....
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
"You who covers himself
[with a garment],"
"Arise and warn."
"And your Lord glorify."
"And your clothing purify, and
uncleanliness avoid."
What is our duty, my Sheikh?
Our Prophet...
did his duty all his life.
He tried hard...
He made a civilization out of the
arid desert.
Our duty is to follow this holy way.
Our duty is to lighten this era's
darkness with oracle's lamps.
But first...
we should enlighten ourselves.
It's because those who can't
enlighten themselves...
can't enlighten the darkness.
For instance...
those who can't be awake...
those who can't wake up...
can't stand this grief.
Those who don't believe...
can't set up a civilization in this world.
Don't forget, friends...
If someone doesn't pray at night, he
can't be a fighter at day.
Now it's time to try hard.
Inshaallah, we'll set up our dervish
convent...
- here.
- Inshaallah.
This dervish convent...
will be a precursor of a new founding.
You're here without any news,
Commander Kongar. Alişar Bey isn't here.
I know.
Why did you come then?
You tell me.
Now tell me...
Where is Alişar?
Alişar Bey went to wherever he wanted.
He accounts for neither me nor you.
I call out...
don't you know? I'll tell you!
My brother.
We have a revenge to take.
We've just started.
What's that? What's happening?
Boran, what are you doing?
Keep calm, Dündar Bey.
Osman Bey wanted me to do it.
Where are you taking them?
Why don't you take me?
What will you do?
Take me.
Take me!
Where are we going, Boran?
What will you do to us?
Tell me.
I do what Osman Bey wants, Dündar Bey.
Forgive me.
Hatun, don't worry.
I'll take care of Aygül, don't worry.
Osman!
Osman, don't!
Don't hurt them! Don't!
Take me. Take me, Osman!
Osman.
- What are you going to do?
- You'll see, uncle.
You'll see when your eyes open
without greed.
Don't hurt them!
Don't!
Kill me. Don't hurt them! Don't hurt my
child and my Bey!
Take me, Osman! Don't!
Kill me instead of them!
Don't!
Princess.
Alişar did this to you?
It's okay.
I'm fine, thanks to you.
Çetinalp, protect Princess.
Take her to where Osman Bey said.
Protect her well.
- Do you understand?
- Don't worry, Konuralp.
Horses are outside. Let's go, princess.
I'm grateful for everything.
God bless you.
I couldn't see their content.
I took all the papers.
- Good, brother.
- Let's go before Alişar comes with his dogs.
Get ready.
Let's go silently
before Alişar and his dogs come.
We took what we had to.
Aygül.
Come with me.
Osman!
Osman, what are you doing?
You know what to do.
I know, Osman Bey.
Aygül!
- Where are you going, my daughter?
- It's time you faced Alişar Bey, father.
- Aygül...
- Sorry, father.
Now, it's time to reveal the truth.
What truth, Aygül?
What the hell are you talking about?
Osman Bey will take you to Alişar Bey.
Forgive me for doing this.
I can't be a wife of someone who I doubt
that may have killed my brother.
Aygül, stop!
Daughter, I'm talking to you!
What do you think you are doing?
Stop!
Daughter!
Forgive me, father.
But I am doing the right thing.
Aygül, come back here!
I won't give you my blessings,
my daughter, come back here!
- Aygül!
- Pull yourself together, uncle.
Aygül doesn't want to marry
her brother's murderer.
She's brave enough to reveal that.
Now, it's your turn to be brave.
You are going to face Alişar.
You are using my daughter to
entrap Alişar.
You are going to pay off, Osman!
I will kill everyone who is with you!
I will be your death!
I will ruin you!
I will call you to account for what you
have done!
Let's go.
There is no sign.
We have been searching in the right area.
I have gone hunting with Osman a lot.
It's hard to find him in the forest.
I am not leaving until I find my sister
and father, Alişar Bey.
You can leave if you have important things
to do.
Aygül is your sister,
and she is my fiance.
Dündar is your father,
and he is my friend.
We are not leaving before we find them.
- There's no use in searching.
- What do you mean, Commander Böke?
Are you saying that we should leave
my sister and father to their fate?
Osman will leave us a trace at the time
when he wants us to find him.
He will draw us where he wants us to be.
We need to take cover.
What's in your mind, Commander Böke?
My Bey, can I?
I will take it all out on you if you
don't say something important.
My Bey, Osman Bey's Alps raided into
your mansion and abducted your guest.
What are you saying!
Talk!
Osman is strating to leave traces.
Let's see who entraps first.
Speak, I tell you!
Speak!
The gate of the mansion was open when I
got there, there were bodies in the yard.
Osman!
This is now a feud.
My Lord, execute either me or Osman!
What are you waiting for, Melik?
Bring the horses!
We are going to drink blood!
I wish to be with you in the revenge day,
Alişar Bey.
But, leave a couple of scouts of yours with
me, we'll inform you if we found anything.
Inform every living in this land!
From now on, everyone who is good with
him...
... or respects him is my enemy!
If someone is brave enough to face me,
let them come.
What do you say, Commander Böke?
It's like I said, if we
follow his traces...
We will end up dead.
But we are going to follow Osman,
not his traces.
Our tribe has been in trouble since
you came here.
Leave Osman alone, you cause trouble
to him.
Alişar Bey.
How did this happen?
How can they get in my mansion freely?
How could you let that happen?
My Bey, It was Kongar.
He came with Nökers(soldiers).
We didn't know he came to abduct
Princess.
- Kongar?
- A wounded man of ours told us.
Nökers(soldiers) were Osman's Alps.
They saw Konur and Boran
disguised as Nökers, my Bey!
Alişar Bey!
I have things that I need to tell you.
"My father is hiding in
a secret place in the forest."
" Osman kidnapped us," he says.
"But he learned something
important about Osman."
"He wants to talk to you where
no one is present."
"I want him to come alone, he said."
"We will finally end Osman together!"
Tell him these.
Osman kidnapped my father and mother.
I know where he is. Only you can save us.
Bismillâhirrahmânirrahîm.
(in the name of God, the merciful and compassionate.)
Bismillâh.
The time of iftar is near.
Let me continue from here, my Sheikh.
Is working your duty and
not mine, my Akça?
Not at all, my Sheikh.
Bismillâh.
My Sheikh!
I've come to your side,
if you accept it.
You've come at a good time, my daughter.
You came after good news.
You've come like the spring after winter.
Welcome.
You brought happiness.
Did the good news fell on
the soil, my Sheikh?
They fell on our hearts, my daughter.
If Allah permits,
we'll build our lodge here.
This lodge will be a warning base,
if Allah permits.
The enemy is wild, trouble is diverse.
But the worst danger awaiting
humans is the fire of hell.
We'll warn.
Because warning is a lovers duty.
How will we warn, my Sheikh?
Like a mother warns her naughty child
of the dangers waiting for him...
Like a master warns his apprentice
of the dangers waiting for them...
Like a doctor treats her patience...
We'll warn the people of Mohammad
the same way in this lodge.
Hopefully, this lodge will be the place
of hope for a new establishment.
In this lodge, we'll enlighten
those who are in the dark.
We'll turn Alps into saints.
From a filthy state, we'll fly
towards a great future.
May our run be blessed, and
our lodge Mubarak!
- Amen.
Boran. We'll cut this malady like
the tumour on my grandfather's back!
- Hopefully, my Bey.
- Hopefully.
- Keep your eyes wide open.
- I will.
My Bey, ambush!
Mountains don't touch other mountains...
But people can reach other
people, Osman.
Aygül!
Aygül! My heart is on Bala Hatun.
I've come this mansion to make Alişar
Bey happy and spend my life by his side.
But don't forget that I came with
my pain, and not with a wedding.
My wedding will be today.
But the ceremony will be
the day Osman dies...
... who killed my brother and
kidnapped my father and mother.
This mansion will mourn until
the fire inside me is cooled down...
... with Osman's blood!
Now take out everything I see
that enhances my pain!
I'll be mourning on my man's mansion.
Remember that!
Aygül is waiting peacefully in her home
for his father to return.
And you...
Looks like the end of the road for you.
Father!
Bahadır!
Where is my father?
You'll feel your father's wrath like
your brother Batur.
Don't.
Bahadır is like a son to me now.
I won't let you take his life like
you've taken Batur's life.
Bahadır!
Children suffer from their father's sins.
Don't. Don't you do it.
Don't you trust that dog Alişar.
You'll dig your father and
sister's grave yourself.
Don't.
They will rip your lungs to pieces when
I throw you to the hands of Geyhatu.
You won't even have a grave.
Osman...
Those who devote their
lives to their people...
... live longer than their executioners!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com